Pat Mifsud

patmifsud@me.com Sydney, Australia Folio: patmifsud.com 0448 742 570

I'm a passionate designer specialising in user interfaces and user experience research.

I believe that great design is visually appealing, solves the right problem for the right person, and is feasible to build.

Experience

UI / UX Designer at The Big Crunch Feb 2019 - Now

I designed interfaces for web and mobile productivity tools, while creating a basic design system for the company in Figma where stakeholders and developers could directly collaborate on designs.

I ran over 40 user tests and interviews for less then \$300.

I swapped hats to design/ growth hacking/ front end development/ customer support as needed as we grew our userbase from two to four figures.

CX Designer at Ailo Sep 2018 - Dec 2018

I worked across disciplines and teams to design and build scalable systems to convert trials to subscriptions and decrease churn.

I designed and built onboarding campaigns and landing pages with the CX team, working with the backend systems (Mailchimp/ Vero) that drove them.

I designed dashboards and reports to keep the sales and engineering teams in touch with their impact on the customer experience through Salesforce and external tools.

Product Owner at LPMA (Owned by Ailo) Feb 2018 - Sep 2018

I worked with domain experts, stakeholders, internal and external engineering and design teams to own and design a business consulting product.

I worked with an external development company to build consulting products and client resources.

Graphic / UX Designer at Apmasphere (Owned by Ailo) Feb 2017 - Feb 2018

I created prototypes and ran usability testing sessions, presenting results to design team, developers and stakeholders.

I learned Framer.js to allow us to prototype complex interactions and animations, validated and iterated on these designs through user feedback.

Graphic Designer at I-MANIFEST Charity 2014 - 2015

Graphic and web designer, probono.

Designer and Marketing Coordinator at Apmasphere (Owned by Ailo) Mar 2015 - Feb 2017

I worked on branding, print and digital design work, video and animation projects, email marketing, physical spaces - designing conference booths, signage and branding.

Graphic Designer at Urban Purveyor Group 2013 - 2015 (Saké, Löwenbräu, The Argyle)

Assistant Teacher at UTS Sydney Feb - May 2014

Education

Bachelor of Design in Visual Communication -University of Technology Sydney

Distinction Averge. I took electives in user experience, animation and frontend programming.

Certificate IV in Graphic Design & Communication WSI, NADC (TAFE)

Folio and case studies: patmifsud.com Referees on request